Rafael Vieweg

London, NW10



vieweg@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/vieweg



+44 7447 485834



https://vieweg.dev

Summary

Hello, my name is Rafael, I am a software engineer full stack based in London. With more than 12 years of experience in developing systems and web applications.

Solid skills in Javascript, typescript, reactjs, nodejs, php, symfony and the entire stack involved.

I am looking for a position of preference in JS / TS technologies.

Experience



Software Engineer

Fixas - Smart Ideas and Solutions

Aug 2014 - Dec 2020 (6 years 5 months)

Fixas is a small company, where I was the only developer, so I worked as Software engineer Fullstack (Frontend and Backend).

- Led meetings with customers and their teams, to raise functional requirements and business rules.
- Developed websites and systems, we used mainly Symfony PHP framework, Wordpress, prestashop and ReactJS.
- Deployed and maintained the websites we mainly use a ubuntu server allocated at DigitalOcean, with continuous integration through github actions.
- Implement new features and fixes.

I left the company when I moved to England.

==> Tech Stack: Javascript, Typescript, ReactJS, Node.js, PHP, Symfony, Postgress, Mysql, Docker, MongoDB, NextJS, Github.



Software Developer

Guiafixas - Websites and Systems Aug 2008 - Aug 2014 (6 years 1 month)

- In this position my main responsibility was to integrate html templates to CMS Wordpress.
- ==> Tech Stack: PHP, JS, JQuery, Mysgl, Wordpress, Html, CSS



Prefeitura de Itajaí

2004 - 2005 (2 years)

Technical support to City Hall systems via telephone and if necessary on site.

Education

Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Project Management 2010 - 2011

Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

Superior, Tecnologo em sistemas para internet, Information Technology 2006 - 2009

Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

Computer Science 2004 - 2006

Skills

Node.js • JavaScript • React.js • Software Development • Web Applications • PHP • SQL • MongoDB • PostgreSQL • TypeScript